# LUCILE TRONCZYK

### FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

San Francisco, California • +33 761591351 • lucile.t.tech@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/lucile-tronczyk • https://github.com/LucileTech

I am a creative Fullstack Developer with a work permit in the United States, eager to get new challenges and learn new things.

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript | Typescript | React JS | NodeJs | NextJs | MongoDb | ExpressJs | CSS | HTML | Axios | Bootstrap | Git |
Github | GitLab | Figma | Bootstrap | Sentry

#### PERSONAL TECH PROJECTS

#### Octopus - Full-stack eCommerce build in pairs in 10 days

Dec 2022

MongodDB, ExpressJs, React, NodeJs, JavaScript, CSS & HTML

Post it - Full-stack Web Application build in pairs in 4 days

Nov 2022

JavaScript, Axios, ExpressJs, NodeJs, HandlebarsJs, MongoDB, CSS & HTML

The Cat and the Fantastic Forest - Small Browser Game build alone in 4 days

Oct 2022

JavaScript, CSS & HTML

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Engineer, Front-End (Freelance), Paris, France

Jan 2023 – Feb 2023

Koalou, App for mental well-being of children - NodeJs, Graphql, Typescript, PostgreSQL, ReactJs, Gitlab, Slack, Figma, Sentry

- Built responsive web pages in React IS and Next IS, using React-Bootstrap
- · Implemented new feature on Frontend Web application built with React and Typescript, with Backend calls
- Collaborated on GitLab
- Implemented redesign of 2 pages, creation of 5 pages
- Reproduction of Figma web designs

### Footage Researcher (Freelance), Paris, France

Sept 2016 – Sept 2022

Main projects: "Solidarnosc" & "After Chaos, Warsaw" directed by Barbara Necek; "2000-2020: 20 years of unforgettable images", "C dans l'air" (Important french News TV Show); "C ce soir" (Debate TV Show)... and more.

- Researched footage and archives in collaboration with the directors or journalists
- · Organized all the footages by sources and themes for the editor and directors or journalists
- Cleared rights and optimized budget allocation for archives over 5 years of C dans l'air TV Shows and 5+ documentaries and telecasts
- Identified steps to reduce archive budget by almost 30%, as find the right sources or improve communication
- Coached and advised other footage researchers in order to work together on projects

### Screenwriter, Script Developer & Coodinator (Freelance), Paris, France

Sept 2015 – Mar 2020

Main projects: Script coordinator for TOP-The Oligarchs Productions; Script developer for EDI Films; Screenwriter of "Image du temps" (Picture of time)

- Coordinated the writing of a TV show with a showrunner and screenwriters team
- Analyzed the potential of projects, did thematic research and press review, read scripts and books for productions
- Screenwrited personal projects, as an award winning produced documentary about passage of time in mining towns of North of France

### **EDUCATION**

#### Fullstack Web Development graduate, Paris, France

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

Ironhack Bootcamp - HTML | CSS | JavaScript (ES6) | React) | ExpressJs | NodeJs | MongoDb | Axios | HBS | Git | GitHub 400 hours of intensive training, 3 projects each build in 4 days, more than 25 labs.

Mastered front end projects using responsive web design with HTML/CSS, JavaScript using ES6, and Bootstrap

Built full stack project using ExpressJs, NodeJs, HandlebarsJs, MongoDB and Axios

Achieved a single page application using the most popular frontend frameworks in the world: ReactJs

### Javascript, CSS, HTML certification, Remote

May 2022 - Aug 2022

Codecademy Online classes of modern technical skills - JavaScript | CSS | HTML

### Master of Arts in Cinema, Paris, France

Sept 2011 - Jun 2016

La Sorbonne Paris 1 - Learned Screenwriting, directoring & Cinema production

### Bachelor of Science of Arts, Paris, France

Sept 2011 - Jun 2016

La Sorbonne Paris 1 - Learned history and making of Cinema and arts

## HIGHLIGHTS

Languages: French and English fluent

Certifications & Training: 6kyu on Codewars, online Fullstack courses on Codecademy, Hacker Rank training

Awards: Won Best Documentary Award for "Image du Temps" (Picture of time) at Sorbonne' 15th Shot Movie Day (2016)